Welcome brothers and sisters to another
Wednesday question and answer where we
open up with the 10 Commandments that
God had written for the whole world to
keep. Brother James. Yes, sir.
And God spoke all these words, saying, I
am the Lord thy God, which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt, out of
the house of bondage. Thou shalt have no
other gods before me. Thou shalt not
make unto thee any graven image, or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above, or that is in the earth beneath,
or that is in the water under the earth.
Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them,
nor serve them. For I the Lord thy God
am a jealous God, visiting the iniquity
of the fathers upon the children unto
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me, and showing mercy unto
thousands of them that love me, and keep
my commandments. Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain. For
the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain.
Remember the Sabbath day to keep it
holy. Six days shalt thou labor, and do
all thy work. But the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In it thou
shalt not do any work, thou, nor thy
son, nor thy daughter, thy man servant,
nor thy maid servant, nor thy cattle,
nor thy stranger that is within thy
gates. For in six days the Lord made
heaven and earth, the sea, and all that
in them is, and rested the seventh day.
Wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day, and hallowed it.
Honor thy father and thy mother, that
thy days may be long upon the land which
the Lord thy God giveth thee. Thou shalt
not kill. Thou shalt not commit
adultery. Thou shalt not steal. Thou
shalt not bear false witness against thy
neighbor. Thou shalt not covet thy
neighbor's house, thou shalt not covet
thy neighbor's wife, nor his man
servant, nor his maid servant, nor his
ox, nor his ass, nor anything that is
thy neighbor's. I read Exodus 20:1-17.
May the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word. In Jesus' name we
pray. Amen.
Amen.
So here on question and answer, you can
ask us a question and we'll answer
according to the King James Bible. And
if we cannot find the answer, we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time. The questions we
will not answer are the vague and the
long scripture questions, as well as the
questions of debate. We are not here to
debate, we are here to spread the true
gospel of Jesus. So please be as direct
as possible with your questions so we
can be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible. No
other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program. Keep in
mind that this also is a live stream, so
feel free to send in your questions that
pertain to everlasting life. We just
asking that you keep your questions to a
two scripture maximum. And let me
introduce you to family that's on the
panel this evening. Brother Jerome.
Grace and peace.
Brother Dre.
Good evening.
Brother Julius.
Good evening, everybody.
Brother James.
Good evening, everyone.
Sister Deborah.
Good evening.
Brother Sean.
And we have the guest caller with us,
and I'm Brother Cornell. Sister Deborah,
what is the first question of our
program?
Uh yes, there are a few held over
questions carried over from October the
15th, 2025
that will be answered now. Valencia
says, can you tell me who are Admah and
Zeboim, and do they relate to Israel's
Hosea 11:8?
All right, so they want to know who is
this Admah and Zeboim in that Hosea 11
and 8.
So let's go there to that book, Brother
James. It's the book right after Daniel,
and the guest caller will take it from
there. Go ahead, brother.
Okay.
Hosea 11:8 says,
How shall I give thee up, Ephraim?
How shall I deliver thee, Israel?
How shall I make thee as Admah?
How shall I set thee as Zeboim?
Mine heart is turned within me, my
repentings are kindled together.
Okay.
Let's go to Deuteronomy, the 29th
chapter,
and read verse 23.
Okay.
Deuteronomy 29 and verse 23 says,
And that the whole land thereof is
brimstone, and salt, and burning,
that it is not sown,
nor beareth, nor any grass groweth
therein,
like the overthrow of Sodom and
Gomorrah,
Admah and Zeboim,
which the Lord overthrew in his anger
and in his wrath.
Okay, so these these two cities, Admah
and Zeboim, are two cities that were
destroyed along with uh uh Sodom and
Gomorrah, because all of them were very
wicked.
Now the Lord is saying to you that he
will not destroy Israel like he
destroyed Admah, Zeboim,
also Sodom and Gomorrah.
That's all he's saying.
I'm not going to do to you what I did to
them.
That's all I have to say.
Mhm. All right. I hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one.
Moving on. Cash in asks, in Revelations
21, the verse that says there was no
more sea, does the word sea mean people
in that verse?
All right, Revelation 21, the verse that
says no more sea, does that mean people?
Brother Jerome.
No.
It's not [clears throat] referring to
the people. It's actually referring to
literal
uh water. A body of water that the Lord
referred to as seas in Genesis.
Okay? So let's go to Genesis, the first
chapter, and read verse 9 and 10. We're
going to tie it with Revelations 20.
Genesis chapter 1, verse 9 and 10. When
you get it, go ahead and read.
Okay. It says, And God said, Let the
waters under the heaven be gathered
together unto one place.
And let the dry land appear, and it was
so.
And God called the dry land earth, and
the gathering together of the waters
called he seas. And God saw that it was
good.
Okay. Now let's go to Revelations 20 and
read verse 13.
Okay.
It says, And the sea gave up the dead
which were in it. And death and hell
delivered up the dead which were in
them.
And they were judged every man according
to their works. Yeah, so these seas are
not people in this case. It's actually
talking about a body of water that the
Lord referred to as seas, like we just
read in Genesis. That's all I got.
All right.
Thank you for that, brother. Hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our next question.
Next question. Danielle Ramsey says,
What is with some of these Hebrew
brothers' calculations
on the Lord's feast day count, and whose
calendar are they following? He says
they keep professing that IOG, which I
follow, is in error.
All right, so regarding the feast days,
and they're saying that we are in error.
Guest caller.
Well,
they're wrong.
First thing is,
we uh we calculate our feasts
uh we uh uh uh
according to Jerusalem time. They
calculate calculate their feasts
according to they talking about barley
in the field, and some of them use
American time.
But we use Jerusalem time.
And that's where we start to calculate.
That's the time when the new moon shows
up in Jerusalem, not in America.
And the reason we use Jerusalem time is
because of what the scripture say.
Let's go first in the Isaiah, the second
chapter, read verses 1 through 3.
Isaiah, the second chapter, verses 1
through 3 says,
The word that Isaiah the son of Amos saw
concerning Judah and Jerusalem.
And it shall come to pass in the last
days that the mountain of the Lord's
house shall be established in the top of
the mountains, and shall be exalted
above the hills. And all nations shall
flow unto it.
And many people shall go and say, "Come
ye, and let us go up to the mountain of
the Lord, to the house of the God of
Jacob. And he will teach us of his ways,
and we will walk in his paths, for out
of Zion shall go forth the law, and the
word of the Lord from Jerusalem."
So, I let you know that whatever the
world is going is
going to be
measured by is going to be measured by
what goes on in Jerusalem.
And so, it said, "Through out of Zion
shall go forth
the word of God."
You know, and so the whole thing is
that includes the time. Now,
let's see what happen when the Lord is
back on this earth because when Jesus
return
we going to see what's going to happen
once he's on this earth. Well, let's go
to Zechariah the 14th chapter and I'll
read verse 1 through 5 first.
Okay.
Zechariah 14 verses 1 through 5 says,
"Behold, the day of the Lord cometh,
and thy spoil shall be divided in the
midst of thee.
For I will gather all nations against
Jerusalem to battle, and the city shall
be taken, and the houses rifled,
and the women ravished. And half of the
city shall go forth into captivity.
And the residue of the people shall not
be cut off from the city.
Then shall the Lord go forth and fight
against those nations as when he fought
in the day of battle.
And his feet shall stand in that day
upon the Mount of Olives, which is
before Jerusalem on the east.
And the Mount of Olives shall cleave in
the midst thereof toward the east and
toward the west.
And there shall be a very great great
valley. And half of the mountain shall
remove toward the north and half of it
toward the south.
And ye shall flee to the valley of the
mountains, for the valley of the
mountains shall reach unto Azal. Yea, ye
shall flee like as ye fled from before
the earthquake in the days of Uzziah,
king of Judah. And the Lord my God shall
come, and all the saints with thee."
Now, this is at the coming of Jesus. He
going to come in the first place his
feet going to hit on this earth is the
Mount of Olives, which was the last
place his feet touched when he left the
earth.
And it said, "And the And he going to go
forth and fight because that's the going
to be the battle of Armageddon."
His feet shall stand on Mount of Olives.
And it said, "The Lord my God shall come
and all the saints with thee." Those are
the people that are in the first
resurrection that met the Lord in the
air, which 1 Thessalonians the fourth
chapter talked about.
And when he come
meet him in the air, all of them going
to come back down to earth.
And the Lord
is going to be in Jerusalem. And skip
down to verse 9 and let's see what what
what what he going to rule. Verse 9.
And the Lord shall be king over all the
earth.
In that day shall there be one Lord, and
his name one."
So, the Lord So, when Jesus come back,
he going to be king over all the earth.
He going to rule this earth from sea to
sea.
There going to be no challenges.
And then look what's going to be
required of the nations. Skip down.
Nations that are left. Skip down to
verse
uh
Look like 15. I can't read my own. 16?
Huh?
16 says,
"And it shall come to pass that everyone
that is left of all the nations which
came against Jerusalem shall even go up
from year to year to worship the king,
the Lord of hosts, and to keep the Feast
of Tabernacles."
Now,
So, now when the Lord come back
everybody got to keep the Feast of
Tabernacles. That's like we keep all the
feasts now.
And what time is he going to keep it? At
the time that the Lord holds it in in
Jerusalem. So, when all the nations come
up, all of them going to keep it on the
same day. You know why? Because all of
them going to have to go to Jerusalem or
somebody that represent them have to go
to Jerusalem. And it's going to be on
the same day. So, now we don't wait
until the Lord come
the day that to
observe the laws and the dates
of Jerusalem. We are doing it now. So,
when we started calculation
for the holy days and for our calendar,
we started with the with the
day that the new moon shows up in
Jerusalem.
Because it's the whole world going to
keep it at one time, and that time is
going to be the time that is in
Jerusalem.
That's all I have to say.
All right.
Hope that answered your question there
as we continue to move on.
Moving on. Sky Rider ask, "How much does
a person have to sin until God decides
he's done with him?"
How much does a person have to sin until
God decides he is done with him?
We'll open this up to the panel.
And um
we can One place we can start when God
is done with you is Romans 1. Let's go
to Romans 1. We just going to read a
couple of scriptures there. Wait a
minute. Wait a minute before you read
anything.
Pay attention to the question. What did
the question say?
Again, the question is, "How much does a
person have to sin until God decides
he's done with him?" That's a God call.
We don't know.
There you go. That's a God call.
Romans and nobody else. No man can tell
you that. Only God.
Okay?
That's a God call.
>> So, as far as
we don't know.
All right.
>> that.
First thing you do when you see the
Lord, ask him.
All right. We'll keep it moving to the
next question. Yes. We going into new
territory, right? Yes, we are now into
tonight's questions from October the
22nd, 2025,
which are carried over to tonight's Q&A
uh for October the 29th, 2025.
Red Wolf ask, "Does Numbers 19 verses 11
through 13 also pertains to every dead
soul, including animals and using their
skins for leather leather or suede shoes
worn daily, or the same for coats worn
in colder weather?"
All right. Brother Julius.
Let's go there, James.
Let's go Let's go there and let's look
at the context of Numbers 19.
Have nothing to do with animals. Has
something to do with clean and unclean
rituals
and how to be clean.
Let's read that scripture. Begin, James.
Numbers 19. And pick it up at verse 11.
Let's see if we got any animals
mentioned here.
Go ahead.
>> 19:11 says, "He that toucheth the dead
body of any man shall be unclean 7 days.
He shall purify He shall purify himself
with it with it on the third day, and on
the seventh day he shall be clean.
But if he purify not himself the third
day, then the seventh day he shall not
be clean.
Whosoever toucheth the dead body of any
man that is dead, and purifieth not
himself, defileth the tabernacle of the
Lord. Uh-huh.
>> And that soul shall be cut off from
Israel because the water of separation
was not sprinkled upon him. He shall be
unclean.
His uncleanness is yet upon him."
So, now the whole chapter deals with
clean and unclean and the waters of uh
separation. So, this has anything This
has nothing to do with
uh
animals or things like that. There other
chapters that deal with that, but this
does This has nothing to do with it.
That's all I got.
All right. We're going to keep it moving
to our next question.
Moving on. Brick Brad wants information
on what her friend said about marriage
in Genesis 24:67
saying, "You are married in God's eyes."
All right. Genesis 24.
Let's go there, Brother James. Pick it
up at that
six Genesis 24:67,
right? Yes.
All right. Let's go there. Read it,
brother, and the guest caller take it
from there.
Okay, Genesis 24:67
says, "And Isaac brought her into his
mother Sarah's tent and took Rebecca,
and she became his wife. And he loved
her, and Isaac was comforted after his
mother's death."
So, so we're going to examine this.
This is one of the old things that
Hebrew Israelites been saying for years.
If you're laying with a woman, she is
your wife.
But it says
Get careful, and he said, "She shall
what?"
It says
>> Read the verse.
Go ahead.
Careful, go ahead and repeat that
question.
All right, the question I
Read the Read the scripture. Okay, it
says, "And Isaac brought her into his
mother Sarah's tent and took Rebecca,
and she became his wife.
And he loved her,
Mhm. And she became his wife.
It didn't say that made her his wife.
Became We're going to examine this a
little bit. We're going to look at first
Let's look at Deuteronomy the 20
uh uh
8th chapter.
Hold on a second.
Deuteronomy chapter 22, rather, and read
verse 28 and 29.
Okay, Deuteronomy 22 and verses 28 and
29 says,
"If a man find a damsel that is a
virgin, which is not betrothed,
and lay hold on her, and lie with her,
and they be found, then the man that lay
with her shall give unto the damsel's
father 50 shekels of silver, and she
shall be his wife.
Because he had
Go ahead.
Because he hath humbled her, he may not
put her away all his days."
Now,
let's go now
to uh
uh uh
Exodus.
Mhm.
Exodus 22
and read verse 16 and 17.
Okay,
Exodus 22 verses 16 and 17 say,
"And if a man entice a maid that is not
betrothed,
and lie with her,
he shall surely endow her to be his
wife.
If her father Uh-huh. Wait, it didn't
say she is his wife, did it?
No.
He shall surely endow
her. He shall surely endow her to be his
wife. Go ahead.
"If her father utterly refuse to give
her unto him, he shall pay money
according to the dowry of virgins."
So, then
then she can't be his wife, isn't that
correct?
Correct.
Cuz he Her father said, "No, uh-uh, you
ain't marrying my daughter." And that's
going to be the end of it.
But the whole thing is, marriage is not
predicated on laying with somebody.
It is
agreements.
You can have a wife and haven't touched
her. Case in point, let's go to Matthew
the 2nd chapter.
Teach.
>> going to read 18 to 20.
But we finished that, right? Yes, we
did.
Okay.
All right. Uh
And that was Matthew, what chapter
again, sir?
Two.
And verses 18 through 20. Okay.
Matthew chapter 2 verses 18 through 20
says, "In Rama was there a voice heard,
lamentation and Wait a minute. Wait a
minute.
Is that Matthew's the 2nd chapter? Yes,
sir.
At verse 18? Yes, sir.
What's it say?
It says,
"In Rama was there a voice heard,
lamentation and weeping and great
mourning." No, not the 1st chapter.
We're going to read about Joseph, right?
When Joseph and Mary
Yeah, the 1st chapter.
Okay.
Matthew 1 verse Matthew 1 verses 18 and
through 20 says, "Now the birth of Jesus
Christ was on this wise.
When as his mother Mary was espoused to
Joseph,
before they came together, she was found
with child of the Holy Ghost.
Then Joseph, her husband, being a just
man and not willing to make her a public
example, was mind minded to put her away
privately.
Okay, he was minded to put her away
because she ended up pregnant with
Jesus.
Go ahead and read.
"But while he thought on these things,
behold, the angel of the Lord appeared
unto him in a dream, saying,
'Joseph,
thou son of David, fear not to take unto
thee Mary thy wife, for that which is
conceived in her is of the Holy Ghost.'"
But the angel called her his wife, and
she was his wife.
I skipped that You You finished the 20th
verse? Yes, I did.
Skip down and read verse 25.
Verse 25 says, "And knew her not till
she had brought forth her firstborn son,
and he called his name Jesus."
So, now
Joseph hadn't even touched
his uh uh uh
Mary. That's why he got ready to put her
away.
But then
how was he going How was he going to put
her away? Had to be some kind of
ceremony involved.
Let's see what's going to happen if you
find some uncleanness. Let's go to
Deuteronomy 24 and read verse 1.
Deuteronomy 24:1 says,
"When a man hath taken a wife and
married her, and it come to pass that
she find no favor in his eyes, because
he hath found some uncleanness in her,
then let him write her a bill of
divorcement, and give it in her hand,
and send her out of his house."
So, now, in order for her him to put her
away, he had to give her a bill of
divorcement.
That means it had to be some kind of
agreement made for
her to become a what his wife
other than just laying together.
It's an agreement. Go to Malachi 2 read
verse 13 and 14.
Okay,
Malachi 2 verses 13 and 14 says,
"And this have ye done again,
covering the altar of the Lord with
tears, with weeping, and with crying
out.
Insomuch that he regardeth not the
offering anymore, or receiveth it with
goodwill at your hand.
Yet ye say, 'Wherefore?'
Because the Lord hath been witness
between thee and the wife of thy youth,
against whom thou hast dealt
treacherously,
yet is she thy companion and the wife of
thy covenant."
There you go. That's the secret right
there, the wife of thy covenant. You
have entered into a covenant, and it had
to be a written covenant. That's why if
you want to get away, according to the
word of God, the law of God, Deuteronomy
24th chapter, you have to give her a
written divorcement.
Sex don't make
a wife or a spouse. Let's go I got two
more places. Let's go into Genesis 2nd
chapter.
Read verse 18,
and then skip down and read verse
to 24.
Okay,
it says, "Genesis 2 and verse 18 says,
'And the Lord God said, It is not good
that the man should be alone.
I will make him an help meet for him.'
Then verse 20
Mhm.
It says, "And the Lord God caused a deep
sleep to fall upon Adam, and he slept.
And he took one of his ribs and closed
up the flesh instead thereof.
And the rib, which the Lord God had
taken from man, made he a woman
and brought her un- brought her unto the
man.
And Adam said, 'This is now bone of my
bones,
and flesh of my flesh.
She shall be called woman, because she
was taken out of man.'"
Go ahead.
"Therefore shall a man leave his father
and his mother and shall cleave unto his
wife and they shall be one flesh.
Do not.
He called her his wife and they didn't
even know what sex was.
They didn't even know they was naked.
Until Satan come up on them and told
them that in the third chapter of
Genesis.
But she was his wife.
But he hadn't touched her.
Like Mary was Joseph's wife.
Do not. If you going
So I'm going to show you what you are if
you decide to sleep with a woman. I'm
going to show you what what you've done.
Let's go into uh uh 1 Corinthians the
7th chapter.
First we're going to read verse 1 and 2.
Okay.
1 Corinthians 7:1-2 says,
Now concerning the things whereof you
wrote unto me,
it is good for a man not to touch a
woman.
Nevertheless, to avoid fornication,
let every man have his own wife and let
every woman have her own husband.
Do not. To avoid a fornication.
What's that?
If you laid with her and she became your
wife, then you ain't committing
fornication.
But then,
if you laid with her
and you haven't gotten formally married
to her,
you are a fornicator. Let me show you
what the Lord said what Paul wrote about
that.
Get down and read verses 8 and 9.
Okay.
Verse 8 says,
I say therefore to the unmarried and
widows,
it is good for them if they abide even
as I.
But if they cannot contain, let them
marry.
Listen. What he saying now?
Listen what he said. But if they cannot
contain, in other words, if you can't
avoid if you can't hold yourself from
having sex, then let them marry. Why? Go
ahead.
For it is better to marry than to burn.
Do not. How can you burn
if if
>> [clears throat]
>> if you when you lay with a woman, she's
your wife?
No, no. You burn because you're
fornicating. 1 Timothy 2.
Sex don't make a marriage.
Covenants make a marriage.
That's all I have to say.
All right.
We hope that answered your question as
we move on with the time check.
Yes, the time is 8:03. She and Quill
Akul Joby says, does Isaiah 3:16
and 17 still apply to women today?
He says, modesty seems to be lacking
more now than before.
If it doesn't apply, what is God's
punishment for women's lack of modesty
in today's world?
All right. Isaiah 3:16 and 17 dealing
with modesty. Brother Julius.
I want to say first of all
that you just can't label this with
women
because men can be the same way. Let's
read the scripture uh
James.
Okay.
Cuz the question is, does modesty still
apply uh or should it still apply today?
Yeah. Yes, my
to
>> To women, yeah.
Go ahead.
Moreover, the Lord said,
because the daughters of Zion are
haughty
and walk with stretched forth necks and
wanton eyes,
walking and mincing as they go and
making a tinkling with their feet.
Therefore, the Lord will smite with a
scab the crown of the head of the
daughters of Zion
and the Lord will discover their secret
parts.
Now,
this is a
this is a scripture that's describing
uh what we call pride today.
What we call va- vanity today cuz that's
all you see.
Satan is the god of this world and all
he has to offer you is the lust of the
eyes, the lust of the lust of the flesh,
and the pride of life. And so that that
because he is the god of this world,
that little g, he is the god of this
world, this is what the people go for.
However, the Lord commands the women to
be modest and that should be applied at
all times throughout all generations.
Not just
uh not just then, but now. But because
Satan is the god of this world, people
gravitate toward that. We in Israel of
God, we have a dress code. A dress code
for the women and a dress code for the
men.
But again, the world does what the world
wants to do with this right here.
Now,
let me show you what the Lord going to
do in the future. What would be the
punishment uh of the people that do
these things? You know, the Lord told
you if you read the read on to the uh
the Lord of
Oh man. Read verse 18 quickly.
In that day, the Lord will take away the
bravery of their tinkling ornaments
about their feet and their cauls and
their round tires like the moon.
Get down to verse 24. So everything that
the world and that the women of the
world thinks is sexy and
and attractive and uh they walking in
pride and in vanity cuz that's all it
is, vanity.
Verse 24.
Go ahead.
And it shall come to pass that instead
of sweet smell, there shall be stink.
Yeah.
>> And instead of a girdle, a rent. Yeah.
>> And instead of well set hair, baldness.
It's coming, yeah.
And instead of a stomacher, a girding of
sackcloth and burning instead of beauty.
And this is talking about the pride of
Jerusalem, sisters and brothers. The
pride of the women, especially our
people of Israel, the Lord going to take
all that away. He already working on it
because now, but it's all about vanity.
Go to the fourth chapter. When the Lord
return, look what he going to do.
Pick it up at verse cuz he going to hurt
this earth and the people on it and look
what he going to do. Read verse 3 and 4
and then we'll be done.
And now, O inhabitants of Jerusalem,
Isaiah 4 and verse 3 and 4.
Okay.
And now, O inhabitants of Jerusalem, oh
I'm sorry. Verse 4 verses 3 and 4. And
it shall come to pass that he that is
left in Zion and he that remaineth in
Jerusalem shall be called holy, Yeah.
even everyone that is written among the
living in Jerusalem. This is your future
when the Lord return. Go ahead.
When the Lord shall have washed away the
filth of the daughters of Zion. See,
they walking in pride now, but the Lord
going to take that away. He going to
deal with all of that when he come back.
Ain't going to be that's not going to go
on in his kingdom. Go ahead. When the
Lord shall have washed away the filth of
the daughters of Zion. Go ahead.
And shall have purged the blood of
Jerusalem from the midst thereof by the
spirit of judgment
and by the spirit of burning. Yeah. Go
ahead.
And the Lord will create upon every
dwelling place of Mount Zion and upon
her assemblies
a cloud and smoke by day
and the shining of a flaming fire by
night.
For upon all the glory shall be a
defense. Cuz the Lord is going to be her
defense.
But
this is what's happening, but yet still
women are commanded to be uh uh uh uh uh
uh to dress modestly. My last place, 1
Timothy 2.
1 Timothy 2.
That's why the book says, train up a
child in the way that they should go.
But because they have no knowledge of
God in the land, the very few have that
knowledge, they don't know. So they
don't do what the world do. When you get
it, 1 Timothy 2, read verse 9
James. 1 Timothy 2 and 9. Go ahead.
In like manner also,
that women adorn themselves in modest
apparel, Oh, there's that modest There's
that modest apparel. It's still we
supposed to do that throughout all
generations.
Go ahead, brother.
with shamefacedness
and sobriety,
not with broiled hair or gold or pearls
or costly array,
Go ahead.
but which becometh women professing
godliness with good works. That's what
the Lord want from his from his people
and from his women.
That's all I got. Anybody want to add to
that?
Uh brother Cornell, you muted.
Great, brother. Thank you for that. I
think they hit the nail on the head as
we move on to our next question.
Yes, moving on. Mary Higgs wants
clarification in ties.
She says, if you apply for a
consolidation loan to pay down bills, is
it required to pay tithes on a loan even
though you're paying that loan back?"
Brother Jerome.
Um well, no.
Uh it's not it's not a earning that
you're talking about. When you when
you're dealing with uh borrowing
money, it's a loan. You're borrowing
money. You know, you don't pay tithes on
money
that you're [clears throat] borrowing,
you know.
Uh
but let's go to uh Proverbs chapter 3
verse 9. You know, you pay tithes on
your increase.
And when you're borrowing money, that's
not a increase. You got to pay that
money back.
Okay.
Um
Proverbs chapter 3 read verse 9, we're
going to tie tie with the Malachi.
Okay.
It says, "Honor the Lord with thy
substance and with the first fruits of
all thine increase." Yeah.
And I go to Malachi 3
and read verse 8 through 10.
Malachi 3 verses 8 through 10 says,
"Will a man rob God?
Yet ye have robbed me.
But ye say, 'Wherein have we robbed
thee?'
In tithes and offerings.
Ye are cursed with a curse, for ye have
robbed me, even this whole nation.
Bring ye all the tithes into the
storehouse that there may be meat in
mine house. And prove me now herewith,
saith the Lord of hosts,
'If I will not open you the windows of
heaven and pour you out a blessing that
there shall be there shall not be room
enough to receive it.'" Mhm. That's all
I got.
All right.
Thank you for that, brother. Hope that
answered their question as we move on.
Moving on. Jennifer Love asks, "Will
Adam and Eve be in the first
resurrection?"
Book doesn't say they will. Book doesn't
say they won't.
So, we can't really make that call, but
we can go to 2 Corinthians, the fifth
chapter. Let's go there.
And let's read about this fair program
given to man. Very fair. Read that 1
verse 10 for me, brother. Go ahead.
2 Corinthians 5 verse 10 says,
"For we must all appear before the
judgment seat of Christ
that everyone may receive the things
done in his body according to that he
had done, whether it be good or bad."
So, that's a God call
on that question that you asked there.
And we will see when that time comes.
That's all I got.
And we hope that that answered your
question, and we're going to move on to
our next one.
Next one. Red Wolf says, "In Deuteronomy
verse 5, pants have a distinctive
characteristic.
If pants are made from feminine fabrics
such as a chiffon or organza,
does that justify a woman can wear what
I say still was created for a man's
wardrobe?"
All right. So,
I noticed they threw in that what I say.
But Drake,
what you say?
Hey, what we say don't matter. What God
says matter.
That's it. That's it. Well, let's go to
that Deuteronomy 22 and read verse 5.
Let's go there and read that.
Go ahead, brother.
It says,
"The woman shall not wear that which
pertaineth unto a man.
Neither shall a man put on a woman's
garment.
For all that do so are abomination unto
the Lord thy God."
Now, today's fashion industry, you know,
you got
uh men with tight pants on. We have a
policy about that. You got,
you know,
clothing that that looks like
it would be for a woman, and some
clothing look like it would be for a
man. However, let's let's go to
Zechariah eighth chapter and look at
something there.
Zechariah 8 and we're going to read
verse 23.
Zechariah 8 and 23.
Go ahead.
>> Zechariah 8 and 23 says,
"Thus saith the Lord of hosts,
in those days it shall come to pass
that 10 men shall take hold out of all
languages of the nations,
even shall take hold of the skirt of him
that is a Jew, saying,
'We will go with you, for we have heard
that God is with you.'"
Now, if you look at a skirt today, a
skirt is like a dress.
But
back in that time, they wore those kind
of garments, and those were for men.
So,
the thing is,
what's a man's clothing and what's a
woman's clothing? I mean, we know to
some degree,
but
you know, that judgment call,
we have to stick with what the book
says.
And it's it's with with the clothing
industry ran by people that it's ran by,
they want to confuse that.
Don't be confused. You come to the
Israel of God, sisters put on a dress,
brothers wear some clothes that that is
appropriate. Don't come in with your
pants sagging, put a belt on, and don't
come in with no super tight pants on.
That's all I got.
Keep it modest, Brother Drake. Yes, sir.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we move on to our next question.
Next question. Skywriter asks, "Will
someone know if they once
and for all have a reprobate mind?"
Will someone know
once and for all if they have a
reprobate mind? Brother Jerome.
Well, we got we got verses that we're
going to read where it says the Lord,
because they have no love for the truth,
Yeah. Um the Lord have given
uh a strong delusion. After the Lord
give them a strong delusion
to believe a lie, they don't even know
that they're dealing with lies.
So, they're not going to know that
they're that they're that the Lord done
made them reprobate, either.
Okay. Uh but let's go read some verses.
Let's go to Romans 1
and we're going to read verse 21, we're
going to skip to 28, and we're going to
tie that with 2 Thessalonians.
Okay.
Romans 1 verse 21 says,
"Because that
when they knew God, they glorified him
not as God,
neither were thankful,
but became vain in their imaginations,
and their foolish heart was darkened."
Read verse 28.
And even as they did not like to retain
God in their knowledge, God gave them
over to a reprobate mind
to do those things which are not
convenient."
That's good. And let's tie that with the
2 Thessalonians
chapter 2
and read verse
10 through 12.
2 Thessalonians chapter 2
verses 10 to 12.
It says,
"And with all deceivableness
of unrighteousness
in them that perish,
because they received not the love of
the truth that they might be saved."
"And for this cause God shall send them
strong delusion that they should believe
a lie." That's the That's the That's the
Lord giving them a reprobate mind.
Go ahead.
"That they all might be damned who
believed not the truth, but had pleasure
in unrighteousness."
And that's that's all I got on it.
All right.
Yes, sir. You don't want to have that
reprobate mind, cuz you are finished if
God give it to you. All right.
We'll go keep moving from there on to
our next question.
Keeping it moving. Mel and Natural
Journey asks, "Is there anything
mentioned in the Bible about Halloween?"
All right. Is there anything mentioned
in the Bible
about Halloween? Brother Julius.
Come off mute, my brother.
My apologies. The word Halloween itself
is not in the Bible.
But, there are things that are pertain
to it that are mentioned. Let's go to
Deuteronomy 18th chapter.
Because the
the
the people look forward to this right
here.
Satan the devil is a master marketer
of death
and deception.
Make it colorful.
Make it attractive.
You know, make it fun.
But, it's deadly.
Deuteronomy 18, we're going to pick this
up at verse 9, James. Deuteronomy 18 and
9. Now, look at all the thing because
you have all your
programming is geared toward what we
call the Halloween season.
Go ahead and read.
It says, "When thou art come into the
land which the Lord thy God giveth thee,
thou shalt not learn to do after the
abominations of those nations." The
abom- Don't do after the abomination.
Wherever the Lord put you, don't do
after the abomination that the nations
do. Go ahead.
There shall not be found among you
anyone that maketh his son or his
daughter to pass through the fire.
Uh-huh. Or that uses divination. Uh-huh.
Or an observer of times. Uh-huh. Or an
enchanter. Uh-huh. Or a witch. You got
grown folks, not just children, grown
folks that dress up as witches.
You got people that dress up like what
they believe to be vampires.
The undead.
Same thing you see on televisions. Same
thing you see at the movies. Continue.
Or a charmer. Or a charmer, uh-huh. Or
consult her with familiar spirits. You
got wizards and warlocks and so on like
that male witches which are warlocks. Go
ahead.
Or a wizard. Or a wizard. Very popular
television
uh
series.
You know,
Harry whatever. But, the people love
this. Go ahead.
Or a necromancer.
Those that chant and deal with the dead.
Go ahead in verse 12.
For all that do these things are an
abomination unto the Lord. Uh-huh. And
because of these abominations, the Lord
thy God doeth drive them out from before
thee. And we get into that kind of
stuff.
Stuff that our fathers knew our
ancestors knew nothing about, now we
into it. So, we have violated what the
Lord told us not to do.
Let one one last place. One last place,
brother Cornell. Let's go to Ephesians
chapter 5.
Ephe- Ephesians chapter 5. I got one
verse there. The Lord said do not don't
do this. But, Satan know how to market
it. That's why the colors change at this
time of year to orange and black.
Cuz all this pagan stuff got their own
colors.
And we love it. We think it's cute. We
dress our children up. Then we partake
in it. Grown folks having Halloween
parties. Go ahead. Ephesians 5 and just
one verse. Look what the Lord say do.
11. Go ahead.
And have no fellowship with the
unfruitful works of darkness. Yes. But,
rather reprove them.
You tell them we should not be involved
in this. This is pagan. It is idolatry.
It is everything to do with Satan's
ministry and we
should not partake in this right here.
Don't dress your your children up. When
you know better, then you do better.
That's all I got.
That's right. And brother Julius, don't
the Lord say he's a God of the living
and not of the dead? Halloween is a
3-day festival. October 31st,
All Hallows' Eve, dealing with the
undead.
November the 1st, All Souls' Day,
dealing with the undead. November the
2nd, All Saints' Day, dealing with the
undead.
Pagan, pagan, pagan, an abomination in
the eyes of the Lord.
Yep. All right. Thank you for that,
brother. And we hope that that answer
your question and
whoever's celebrating will take heed.
All right. Let's move on to our next
question with the time check.
Yes, time is 8:25
and our man going ask, "On the Sabbath
day, can we make cold sandwiches?"
Sure, you can make you some cold
sandwiches on the Sabbath day.
Because um
the day before the Sabbath is the day
that you should be planning.
You know, so if you made your turkey,
you don't get up there Saturday and
start carving all your turkey. You
should do that on the day before.
So, let's go let's read Isaiah 58 and
see how special this day is. Isaiah 58
and 13.
You plan. That's what the Sabbath is.
The day before plan on how to
rest and relax and chill with God on
that day.
Your shirt is wrinkled and need ironed
and don't say I'm going to get up on the
Sabbath day and iron it. You should be
ironing it on Friday.
13.
Go ahead, brother.
Isaiah 58 and 13 says, "If thou turn
away thy foot from the Sabbath,
from doing thy pleasure on my holy day,
and call the Sabbath a delight,
the holy of the Lord,
honorable,
and shall honor him, not doing thine own
ways,
nor finding thine own pleasure, nor
speaking thine own words." All right.
So, this this day here is the Lord is
saying that hey, it is a holy day. It's
supposed to be a delight to all those
that take part in it. It's supposed to
be honorable. You're supposed to honor
him and not doing your own ways, nor
finding your own pleasures, nor even
speaking your own words. So, yeah, you
can make you some cold sandwiches. Just
don't do no more than than necessary and
begin your planning on Friday for your
meal for Saturday on the Sabbath. That's
all I got.
We hope that that answered your question
and we're going to move on.
Moving on. Clinton Grant asked, "Is
wearing jewelry a sin?"
Is wearing jewelry a sin?
All right. Let's go in Ezekiel. We'll
open it up to the panel.
Let's go into the Ezekiel 16 first. Go
right ahead, guest caller.
Question is no.
No. Unless what is it?
1 John 3 and 4. Read it.
It says, "Whosoever committeth sin
transgresseth also the law. For sin is
the transgression of the law."
And nothing else.
That's all I have to say.
All right. We'll move on to our next
question.
Next one. Jennifer Love asked, "Is there
a lesson on forgiveness?"
Yeah, a lot of them.
Yes. If you type in on YouTube IOG
forgiving,
and you will find a lot of lessons about
forgiveness and
so forth and so on.
There's a lot of lessons. I I just typed
it in.
There's a lot of lessons on forgiveness.
IOG forgiving and on YouTube. And you
will find a lot of lessons. Felix Drake,
Jackson, Dallas? Yeah. Do you all got a
lesson on forgiveness? Yes.
Mhm.
All right.
We're going to move on to our next
and go right ahead.
It come to forgiveness.
Let us show you why. It's found in the
Lord's prayer. Yes, sir. Let's go into
Matthew the 6th chapter and read verses
12 through 15.
Okay.
Matthew 6 verses 12 through 15 says,
"And forgive us our debts, as we forgive
our debtors.
And lead us not into temptation, but
deliver us from evil.
For thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever. Amen."
"For if ye forgive men their trespasses,
your heavenly Father will also forgive
you.
But, if you But, if you forgive not men
their trespasses, neither will your
Father forgive your trespasses."
That's And that's something you might
take in mind.
That's all I have to say.
All right. We're going to keep it
moving.
Yes, here's another one on lesson. Me
too for you Jones asked, "Do you have a
lesson regarding Paul and his teaching
of Christ more in depth? And he also
asked, "How long had Christ risen before
he visited Paul?"
Guest caller.
Answer to both of them is no and no.
All right. to say.
I guess we'll keep it moving from there,
sister Deborah. Moving on. Barbara still
says, "If there's no close of probation,
why did it say find me while I still may
be found?"
All right. Find me while I still may be
found. Good words of advice for Julius.
Go ahead.
Yes. They're looking for the word The
word probation is not in the Bible.
That's not in the scriptures. Let's go
to Isaiah the 55th chapter. Cuz this is
where she's quoting from.
Mhm.
It's I look at some of these preachers
and they try to make the
They put the the word of God in their
context and and and and really make it
godly, but it's not.
Isaiah 55
James, let's read verses uh uh uh uh
6 through
Let's read 6 through 9. Because
>> Okay. this is a suggestion. This is what
what you should do.
The Lord suggesting this. Just like
just like he It's just like uh We You
know, we verse 1. And then we'll skip
down here. Go ahead.
Okay. It says,
"Ho,
everyone that thirsteth. Yeah. Come ye
to the waters. Yeah. And he that hath no
money,
come ye, buy, and eat. Yea, come, buy
wine and milk without money and without
price."
And so he's telling you come. In other
word, we Come get the word of God.
Come Why you spending your Why you
spending your money on these churches
and paying all these big ties and you
ain't getting fed? It's a suggestion.
It's a question. Now, here's a Here's a
statement here. Verse 6. All the way
down to verse 6. Go ahead.
"Seek ye the Lord while he may be found.
Uh-huh. Call ye upon him while he is
near." He told the the parable of the 10
virgins. Five was wise and five was
foolish.
The five wise The five was wise kept got
that oil, the word of God. The five was
foolish, you know, all that They didn't
get enough oil. So, when they ran out,
that's the word of God.
They came,
but the the five wise virgins said, "We
We can't give you our oil because if we
give you our oil, we won't have enough
for ourselves."
So, he told you, "Seek the Lord while he
may be found.
Call you upon him while he is near." Go
ahead.
"Let the wicked forsake his way. Yes.
And the unrighteous man his thoughts.
>> Come on, James. And let him return unto
the Lord.
And he will have mercy upon him and to
our God, for he will abundantly pardon."
That's not no probation. The Lord is
telling you to repent. Seek him. Serve
the Lord while you can.
Go ahead.
"For my thoughts are not your thoughts.
Keep it.
>> Neither are your ways my ways, saith the
Lord." One more.
"For as the heavens are higher than the
earth, so are my ways higher than your
ways. And my thoughts than your
thoughts." So, when the probation
question came in, I recognized where it
came from.
Come out The door shut up on Noah in the
days of Noah. Noah preached 120 years,
but the people was extremely wicked.
The Lord saved Noah.
So, hey.
He was a righteous man. The
He saved himself and his family through
his righteousness. Just like us right
here. We are seeking the Lord every day
of our life. We should be. Why? Cuz the
Bible says, "Study to show thyself." We
go by the word of God. We don't go by
clever uh sayings and cliches.
You know, uh probation. That is a
Seventh-Day Adventist teaching.
I recognized where it came from. I saw
the program. It is not biblical.
The Lord will have mercy on who he will
and you have a choice. Live or die.
That's it. That's all I got.
I got something I want to point out.
All right. Go to Revelation Go to
Revelation 20th chapter.
Read from 4 to 47.
Okay. Revelation 20 verses 4 through 7
says,
"And I saw thrones, and they sat upon
them, and judgment was given unto them.
And I saw the souls of them that were
beheaded for the witness of Jesus and
for the word of God, and which had not
worshipped the beast, neither his image,
neither had received his mark upon their
foreheads or in their hands, and they
lived and reigned with Christ a thousand
years."
Now,
listen. Go finish Go ahead.
"But the rest of the dead live not again
until the thousand years were finished.
This is the first resurrection.
Blessed and holy is he that hath part in
the first resurrection. On such the
second death have no power.
But they shall be priests of God and of
Christ and shall reign with him a
thousand years."
Yep. Now,
and during that whole thousand years,
the Lord is going to be teaching and the
doors are open for anybody whosoever
will, let them come.
Now,
I'm going to answer the question
directly. Go to the white throne
judgment. Where does it What's Where
does it start? 11th verse? Verse 11.
Yes. Go ahead.
It says, "And I saw a great white throne
and him that sat on it. From whose face
the earth and the heaven fled away. And
there was found no place for them.
And I saw the dead, small and great,
stand before God. And the books were
opened.
And another book was opened,
which is the book of life. And the dead
were judged out of those things which
were written in the books according to
their works.
And the sea gave up the dead and the sea
gave up the dead which were in it. And
death and hell delivered up the dead
which were in them. And they were judged
every man according to their works.
And death and hell were cast into the
lake of fire. This is the second death.
And whosoever was not found written in
the book of life was cast into the lake
of fire."
That's when he can't be found.
Because it's all over with. There you
go.
>> Everybody's waiting.
Everybody's going to be where the Lord
want them to go.
The ones that white throne judgment is
done away with and everybody that's
going to be God going to be God and
everybody that's going to the lake of
fire is in the lake of fire,
that's when he can't be found. It's over
with.
Don't have to say.
All right.
We'll move on to
next question.
Next question. King Likable I Shuff Woo
asked, "What do you do if you are
supporting someone to start a business
and they use the money to rear unclean
animals like pork or breed catfish. Do I
back away from helping them with that
particular business?"
Yes, caller.
Let's go to Leviticus the 20th chapter
and read verse 25.
Leviticus 20
and verse 25 says,
"Ye shall therefore put difference
between clean beasts and unclean.
And between unclean files and clean.
And ye shall not make your souls
abominable by beast or by fowl or by any
manner of living thing that creepeth on
the ground, which I have separated from
you as unclean."
The Lord let you know he's the one that
separated thing from unclean.
Okay?
And now,
let's see something as far as you
getting involved in dealing with that.
Let's go to the First Corinthians 8th
chapter. We're going to read from 9 to
12.
Okay. First Corinthians the 8th chapter
verses 9 through 12 says,
"But take heed lest by any means this
liberty of yours become a stumbling
block to them that are weak.
For if any man see thee, which hath
knowledge, sit at meat in the idols'
temple, shall not the conscience of him,
which is weak, be
emboldened to eat those things which are
offered to idols?
And through thy knowledge shall the weak
brother perish, for whom Christ died?"
Now, see the whole thing is Mhm. Go Go
finish What Did you finish 12? No, that
was verse 11.
Go yeah.
But when you sin so against the brethren
and wound their weak conscience, you sin
against Christ.
So now, you knew that you ain't supposed
to eat pig. You know you ain't supposed
to eat catfish.
And now when you have somebody raise
them and put them on the table,
then you are going against things that
you know better.
And you causing other people to stumble
because they say, "Well, you know, he
know what you supposed to eat because he
he know the Bible."
So I'm going to give you one warning and
you can
decide what you should do.
Let's go to Hebrews the 10th chapter.
Read verses 26 to 27.
Hebrews 10
verses 26 to 27 says,
"For if we sin willfully after that
which we have received the knowledge of
the truth, there remaineth no more
sacrifice for sins.
But a cer- certain fearful looking for
of judgment and fiery indignation which
shall devour the adversaries."
So you know
what sin is. You know what the Lord said
eat and what the Lord said don't eat.
So now, if you going to help produce it
and put it on the table,
then you are sinning willfully
after you have received the knowledge of
God cuz so you know. So now,
the 27th verse tell you where you going.
So it's up to you. Do what you feel is
right. That's all I got to say.
All right.
We hope that that answered your question
as we continue to move on to our next
one.
Next question, JC wants explanation on
why there are differences in the names
listed in Jesus' genealogy
in Matthew 1 verses 1 through 17
and Luke 3 verses 23 through 38.
Uh he says, "I heard these differences
are used to challenge the reliability
of a gospel
and question Jesus' legitimate descent
from King David."
All right. So, JC before
Hey,
I'm not I don't know if you're familiar
with our rules and that, but uh
you're asking us to read 32 scriptures
there, 32 verses. And uh that's not
likely to happen.
So, we're going to ask Brother Julius if
you could trim that down and share some
light on that question.
Okay, because of the content of the
scriptures, I'm going to give you First
of all, I'm going to I'm going to I'm
going to answer his question, Cornel,
about what he heard the difference used
to challenge the reliability of the
gospel and question Jesus' legitimate
descent from David.
Whoever said that don't have no
understanding of the word of God.
No understanding of the word of God
because the scriptures as concluded, we
have not followed cunningly devised
fables. That's what he told you out of
Peter. That's what Peter said. Now,
to give you a quick answer,
when you read the genealogy
uh uh uh of Jesus
from Matthew's perspective,
it is the names are different because
Matthew 1 through 17 explains the key
people
in the lineage of Jesus from Abraham
to Jesus.
Okay? From Abraham to Jesus. That's why
the names are different. When you read
Matthew 1 through 17,
but when you look the names in Jesus'
genealogy, when you look in Luke the 3rd
chapter,
23 to 38,
those names represents
the sons of God from Adam to Jesus.
That's why you see the different names.
That's why the difference is in the
name.
Luke explains Jesus' genealogy from Adam
to Jesus under the title the sons of
God. That's why I tell you which was the
son of Adam, which was the son of God.
Jesus is the son of God.
When you go to Matthew 1 through 17, it
takes you Jesus' genealogy from Abraham
to Jesus.
That's why you see the differences in
the names. But that has nothing to do
with the legitimacy of Jesus cuz Jesus
was a Jew of the tribe of Judah and so
was David.
But they both is Abraham's seed.
So, because people don't understand how
the scriptures is written, how the
genealogies go, they they say, "Well,
that questions the legitimacy of the
gospels and of the Bible." Uh-uh. No,
no, no, no. Jesus told you Let's go to
last that Revelation 22.
Revelation 22.
We going to put Jesus himself on the
witness stand.
Pick it up at 22 and 16. 22 and 16.
This is a warning here about Be careful
the people that you listening to. They
ain't reading the scriptures. Stick
Stick with the Israel of God.
Revelation 22:16. Go ahead, James.
"I Jesus have sent my angel to testify
unto you these things in the churches.
Uh-huh. I am the root and the offspring
of David Uh-huh. and the bright and
morning star."
Verse 19.
He said, "I'm the root and offspring of
David." There's your answer right there
for anybody that said that Jesus didn't
come through David.
Go ahead. Now, verse 19.
"And if any man shall take away from the
word
>> 18, James. Read quick.
"For I testify unto every man that
heareth the words of the prophecy of
this book, if any man shall add unto
these things, God shall add unto him the
plagues that are written in this book.
What else?
And if any man shall take away from the
words of the book of this prophecy, God
shall take away his part out of the book
of life
and out of the holy city and from the
things which are written in this book."
And everybody that lie on the word of
God and assume the word of God, hey, and
you can't read it out of the book,
hey, you going to be fuel for the fire.
On your own, read Isaiah 45 verses 18 to
19. He will tell you, "I the Lord speak
things that are right." That's all I
got, Brother Cornel.
Okay. Let me add some, too.
Uh
if you look in Matthew
1, it traces uh
it traces to Solomon,
the son of David.
Let me see. That's Matthew's 1, right?
Yeah, in verse 6.
In that In that Matthew's 1 verse 6,
it says, "And Jesse begat David the king
and David the king begat Solomon."
But when you go to Luke,
Luke the 3rd chapter,
you pick it up at verse 31,
and it says, "Which was the son of
Melea, which was the son of Menan, which
was the son of Matatha, which was the
son of Nathan,
which was the son of David."
Cuz David had a lot of children.
Yeah. Okay. So, you see a trace from
Solomon in
Matthew,
but you see a trace from one of David's
other sons, which was called Nathan, in
the Luke.
Okay? So, that that there's a difference
right there.
I just wanted to point that. Again, one
genealogy comes from Abraham through to
Jesus
through the lineage, and then the other
one in Luke deals with the son the
lineage Jesus
uh through the sons of God.
All right.
All right. We thank y'all. The light has
come on and we hope that you received
it. As we move on to our next question
with the time check.
Yes, the time is 8:49. We are now
into tonight's Q&A for Wednesday,
October the 29th,
2025.
Detroit Price asks, "In Revelations 19
verse 13,
was this talking about Jesus?"
All right. We're going to open some of
these questions open to the panel cuz we
are
definitely running short on time.
Revelation 19.
And what verse?
13. And verse 13, brother, when you get
there,
read that.
And why don't you pick it up at verse 11
and read down to 13 cuz they want to
know if this is Jesus. Go ahead.
>> Okay. Revelation 19 and 11 through 13
says, I saw heaven open and behold a
white horse. And he that sat upon him
was called faithful and true.
And in righteousness he doeth judge and
make war.
His eyes were as a flame of fire and on
his head were many crowns. And he had a
name written that no man knew but he
himself.
And he was clothed with a vesture dipped
in blood and his name is called the word
of God.
Yes, this Jesus open to the panel.
Anybody else? Yep, that's Jesus. John
1:1 tell you in the beginning was the
word and the word was with God and then
14 tell you and the word was made flesh
and we beheld his glory. This is Jesus.
Yeah, and and if we read that verse 16
James also. Go ahead. Okay, verse 16
says, and he had on his vesture and on
his thigh a name written, king of kings
and lord of lords. Yep.
So,
your answer to that question, yes, that
is Jesus
that we talking about in that 13th
uh verse.
All right. Sister Deborah, next
Next one, Shaniquola Akujo B asks, in 1
Timothy 2 verse 11 and 12 it says, women
should learn in silence with all
submission.
Does that mean women shouldn't share,
talk or even give their understanding
about the gospel word on their social
media page?
No, that's not what that mean but let's
go read that 1 Timothy 2 read 11 and 12.
Let's also open that up to the panel.
Okay.
It says,
let the woman learn in silence with all
subjection.
But I suffer not a woman to teach nor to
usurp authority over the man but to be
in silence.
All right, open to the panel.
Somebody go and read what the Lord say
he going to pour his spirit up on
his sons and daughters on all flesh.
Yep.
Joel 2.
Yep, he told you that in Joel.
Yeah. Mhm.
All right.
In Joel, okay. Let's go there then.
Go there.
Okay.
>> the book and verse?
Uh still searching on that.
Yeah, Joel 2.
Yeah, Joel 2. Yep, Joel 2 and 28. Okay.
Joel 2 and 28 says,
and it shall come to pass afterward that
I will pour out my spirit upon all flesh
and your sons and your daughters shall
prophesy.
Your old men shall dream dreams, your
young men shall see visions.
Same thing in Acts, the second chapter.
Yeah.
But that all over in Joel?
That was verse 28. Did you want me to
read further? Yeah.
>> Yeah.
And uh verse 29 says, and also upon the
servants and upon the handmaids in those
days will I pour out my spirit.
And I will show wonders
Go ahead. in the heavens and in the
earth, blood and fire and pillars of
smoke.
The sun shall be turned into darkness
and the moon into blood before the great
and the terrible day of the Lord come.
Okay, so that's all right.
That's all for and to the
to the women, right? Handmaid, right?
Correct.
Now go to Acts.
You want it directly Acts 2 and same
thing.
2 and 18 directly.
Okay. Acts 2 and 18 says,
and on my servants and on my handmaidens
I will pour out in those days of my
spirit and they shall prophesy.
And I will show Oh, mhm.
And I will show wonders in heaven above
and signs in the earth beneath, blood
and fire and vapor of smoke.
Okay, that's enough. So, he say he going
to pour out his spirit up
his the
sons and the daughters, right? And the
handmaid. Yeah.
Yeah, 17, yeah. One more thing is the
woman just cannot usurp the authority of
a man.
But of course, the Lord expect you to
teach his word and
shoot his word to anybody
if you a woman.
Somebody needs some truth and you got
the answer, you give it to them.
You just not supposed to get up and hit
up no congregation.
Mhm.
That's all that is. All right.
And we have just shown that in the old
as well as in the new testament.
All right, next one Deborah.
All right, and these are a lot of
scriptures.
Emma Joy Israel
uh asks, in Genesis 12 verse 7,
17 verse 1,
18 verse 1 and 2 and 22,
Jesus appeared to Abram. And then she
gives John 5 verse 37.
Are [snorts] there any other precepts to
prove this is Jesus?
And does this mean that every instance
it says the Lord appear
that is Jesus?
All right, we um
not going to cover all those scriptures
but go ahead get started.
Say get your
John 5 and 37 and the other end of it.
That that is all.
Yes, sir.
John 5 and 37
John 5 and 37 says,
and the Father himself which has sent me
has borne witness of me.
Ye have neither heard his voice at any
time nor seen his shape.
So, any time cover all time.
So,
so
all of others
the
all other scripture that refer to God,
what he said and who who and how they
saw him, it's to Jesus. Go to 1
Corinthians 15 the
10th chapter and start reading at verse
1.
Okay.
1 Corinthians 10 verse 1 says, moreover,
brethren, I would not that ye should
have be ignorant how that all our
fathers were under the cloud and all
passed through the sea
and were all baptized into Moses in the
cloud and in the sea and did eat all the
same spiritual meat and did all drink
the same spiritual drink. For they drank
of that spiritual rock that followed
them and that rock was Christ.
So, now
all the scripture, whatever you name,
for the Lord is talking in the old
testament is Jesus. Blank blank. You
ain't never heard the
voices voices at any time or seen his
shape. So, the only one left is Jesus.
And he told you in John 5 and 39, search
the scriptures and they are they that
testify of me.
Also in John 8 it said, Abraham, your
father Abraham rejoice to see my day and
he saw it and was glad.
And the Jews said, you not even 50 and
you seen Abraham? And he said, before
Abraham was, I am.
Yes, sir.
Indeed. All right. Good add on there,
brothers, as we get down to our last
question, Deborah. This is it.
Yes. Uh JT asks,
is the digital ID part of a mark of a
beast as what everyone's been saying?
Digital ID
and mark of the beast, do they have any
comparison? Open to the panel.
Mark of the beast is not no computer.
>> [laughter]
>> Mhm. No computer.
Nope.
So,
no, those those are different
comparisons there.
Different comparisons.
All right, sister Deborah, can we have a
time check?
Yes, the time is 8:59.
8:59. All right.
We have run out of time. We want to
thank everybody from all around the
world who sent in those questions
and we thank you.
And we say that if you submitted a
question we didn't get to it, please
don't resubmit it. Sister Deborah take
it and put it in rotation and we'll
address that question next week. So,
until we all come together again, we say
be safe out there, be blessed, stay
prayed up and may the Lord have mercy on
us all as brother James closes us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread, and
forgive us our debts as we forgive our
debtors. And lead us not into
temptation, but deliver us from evil,
for thine is the kingdom, and the power,
and the glory forever. In Jesus' name we
pray. Amen.
Amen.